The capital letters forms the word "HINT", if you type HINT you would get a hint.

The first hint was some lines from Wikipedia about ASCII.
The given code was in ASCII and you had to convert it using some website.

The second hint was about capital letters, again. It was forming the word "BASE64".
The given code was in BASE64 and you had to convert it using some website.

The paper was giving the website to get the valuable. You suppose to go to that website and get
the actual valuable from there. 

That's all.
